'PADAYAPPA'
Padmashri Dr. Sivaji Ganesan
Super Star, Rajnikanth
Ramya Krishnan
Soundarya
Lakshmi
Sitara
Radha Ravi
Nasir
Manivannan
Senthil
Abbas
Prita
Anu Mohan and N.S. Ramesh Kanna
Vadivukkarasi and Sathyapriya
Mansur Ali Khan and Prakashraj
Vasu Vikram and Prakashraj
Rajeshkumar and Vijayasarathi
Lavanya and Anitha
Story - Arunachala Story Division
Art - G. K
Sound - A. Kodandapani
Costumes - V. Murthy, V.Sai
Stills - Muthupandian
Choreography :. Tarun Kumar, Brinda
(Sakthi Sakthi) and Lalithamani
Fights - Kanal Kannan
Swear on Lord Muruga and tell me...
Are you willing to marry this girl?.
Yes I am willing.
Are you willing to marry this man?.
Are you feeling shy?.
If you say yes, only then this
marriage will take place.
Raise your head and look at me.
So, are you not interested
in this marriage.
No, I'm in love with someone.
She's a small girl, lets
proceed with the ceremony,...
... everything will be
alright after marriage.
See our fate, we can't live
with the person we liked...
... and we can't go against
the wishes of our elders.
I'm not worried about dying
but see we can't even die...
... with the person we like.
Let them atleast forget us
and be happy.
As a repentance for my sin,...
... I am giving half of
my property to the temple.
Such a thing should not
happen in our village again.
The well that they fell in
should not be opened again.
Here after whoever gets
married in this village,...
... whether rich or poor,
should swear on God...
...that they are
willing to get married.
Our family will give dowry...
... and conduct the
marriage in this temple.
After me, my generation
will take over...
... and do the same,
that is my wish.
After marriage every
thing will be fine.
You conduct the marriage.
I can't change the ritual...
... which has been happening
for ages in our village.
In every marriage that takes
place in the village,...
... the bride and the groom's
opinion is more important than...
... the parents opinion.
No marriage will take
place against their wishes.
My family will not
conduct such a marriage.
According to our village rule,...
... your daughter should
marry the man she likes.
Beyond this if this
marriage takes place,...
... your family will
be out of this village.
Your children's life is more
important than your life,...
... so instead of them
falling into the well,...
... the thali that is
going to bind them,...
... should be put into the well,
that is our village rule.
Open that well.
Snake...snake... snake....snake...
Why are they shouting like this?.
Women are bravely pouring
milk for the snake,...
... you men are so
scared......aaaaaaaaa
Madam!
You thought this is a bullock
cart to run across like this.
For the speed I travelled,...
... you would have been
thrown out near that hill.
Fools....
Sorry....we came running
like this because of a snake.
There's that snake.....Snake......
Kill that snake.
Please don't kill that snake,
it won't do anything.
Take your hand.
You're my servant, how dare
you hold my hand and talk.
What are you waiting for,
kill that snake.
Please don't do that....
O God please help....
Aarupadayappa please help me....
Amma its like a temple,
so... Just do what I say.
Walk like a lion
and climb the peak...
If you reach the peak,
climb to the sky...
Who are you man?.
Padayappa, the song was super.
Now...our village youngsters
are struggling to hit the pot.
What to do?.
I feel ashamed.
Are you going to hit
the pot or shall I go?.
No... I do it!
God bless you!
Take this!
- Padayappa....
- What is it?.
Your father.
- I'll tear you to pieces...
- Why are you scolding him now?.
Ask him why he came here,
leaving his job in the city.
Big collectors job...
he's working day...
... and night as a mechanic.
He has studied B.Com engineering.
So he should take up
some contracts and do.
Uncle, thats not B.Com
thats B. E. Engineering.
Thats what I said.
After studying all this why
should he work like that there.
Do you think I want him to
do all that work there.
If he's here, he'll be roaming
with all the fellows...
... and creating problems,
thats why I sent him to the city.
Why do you think I sent
him for such a job,...
... if he works hard only,
he'll know the meaning of life.
My sons what are
they doing, nothing.
- What about you?.
- What are you doing?.
He doesn't even have the
manners to answer me.
When elders are talking,
I should respect them.
- Yes thats right. Whats right?.
- Who said thats right?.
Hey listen to me......
Why are you scolding him, he's
only taken leave and come here.
Again he'll......
How do you know that
he's come on leave.
I wrote to him asking him
to attend my engagement.
I anticipated that.
Who gave you the
guts to do all this?.
Mother....
Who?.?.?.?.
Mother only asked
me to write to him.
Is it so?.
What, is it so?.
You have blood pressure.
Take your medicine.
Please have your medicines!
You trapped me!
Why are you getting
angry with me,...
... we wrote to him
only because he told us.
Nothing will happen in this
house without his consent.
Who is that person?.
Don't talk like that,
see he's looking.
Okay, okay, when a function
is happening in our house...
... I wanted him to be here.
That doesn't mean you have
to tell it before everyone.
Already your son is naughty,
if he knows that I'm soft on him,...
... he'll become worse.
Yehhhhhhh.....
Brother, you itself
asked him to come...
... and now your pretending
that your angry with him?.
Very good acting.
Teach us also to act.
You teach them to act.
Go from here now.
- Your blood pressure will shoot up.
- Shut up.
Wait..
- Do you eat well?.
- Yes father.
Or are you roaming about?.
No father.
Its a long time since
I've seen you,...
... thats why I asked you to come.
- After the function is over,
don't go immediately. - Okay.
- You can stay over here for a month.
- Okay.
I want to see the way
you usually salute.
- Not before you. Do it my son.
- No.....
Thats my son.
- Chinrasu bring my shawl.
- Yes, I'm coming.
The shawl is ready, take it.
Why did you slap me?.
After all I only obeyed your orders.
Don't you know that
I've changed my party?.
There are more party flags
than the national flag.
- It's late, please have your dinner.
- Let my daughter come!
- I'll go call her and come.
- Don't bother her, let her come.
- You come and have your food.
- No, let my sister come.
Everyone don't pamper her.
Only after her birth,
we became rich,...
... not after I married you,
so we have to wait for her.
What is this?.
We have a party meeting
today so I'm getting ready.
- Don't forget the verse I told you.
- No I won't.......
We thought you were dancing
and came running eagerly.
Its the tape recorder.
Okay, okay.
She is a modern girl,
how can you expect her...
... to dance classical dance?.
It's the jet age, you see!
Am I right dear?.
Green...shawl
What are you thinking, dear?.
- A six feet snake...
- Snake....snake.....where
When I just uttered the word
you people are shivering.
One guy caught it in his hand
and even kissed it.
- What a brave man!
- Who is it madam?.
His name is Padayappa.
Oh. Its Arupadayappan.
You mean.... him.
When he was only six years old,
he held a snake in his hand.
He's my sister son.
Didn't you tell her?.
In your childhood,
you used to play with him.
Is Padayappa educated?.
He is the only person
in this village,...
... who is equally educated as you.
He's very sensible,
smart, enthusiastic.....
He is a very nice boy!
- Take that flower off your head.
- No, madam it was very pretty...
I said take it off.
Put it down.
Whatever blooms, grows
and even what I see is mine.
If anyone else trys to take it,
this is what will happen.
I'll destroy it.
Go bring coffee.
Nothing mother.
Nothing, now we have
nothing with us.
Once upon a time,
we had all the luxuries...
... but all we have
now is our honour.
So don't long for anything.
We can only water the flower,...
... don't desire to
keep it on your head.
Okay, go and give coffee.
Wait...turn.
You may go now...
- Who is that girl?.
- Girl!?.
So, so long you played the
organ thinking of a girl.
Then, you want him to think of you?.
- Who is that girl?. Thats what
I'm asking?. - Which girl?.
That girl standing when
I caught the snake.
Your uncle's daughter.
You don't even have an
uncle! She's your cousin.
- What?. My uncle's daughter?.
- Yes.
Yes, she has studied abroad.
She is a very arrogant
and bold woman.
She doesn't seem like that.
Don't you know the way she
came and got down from the car.
That girl came by flight,
and the car came by ship.
Can't imagine the
way she's behaving.
I'm not talking about that girl,
I'm talking about the other girl.
- What are you blabbering?.
- It's Sanskrit.
It is the language of the Gods.
There are three types of women,...
... Sathvigam,
prachothagam, bhayanakam.
We don't understand anything.
- Explain to us!
- I'll explain.
I'll tell you, if you feel
like worshiping a girl...
... when you see her,
its called sathvigam.
When you see a girl,
if you feel like......its called
- We've understood.
- lndeed! It's 'Prachotakam'
When you see a girl, if you get
scared its called 'bhayanakam'.
Okay Padayappa, tell me
which category the girl...
... you saw belongs to.
Sathvigam. The girl who thanked
me when I saved the snake.
From the time I saw her,
I've lost my heart.
Sathukudi..... No.....
Sambar....... No...
Is it sathvigam?.
Yes. Then call her.
Where's my mouth organ?.
Its in your hand.
- He really loves that girl.
- Then we'll get them married.
Give an idea.
I'm not ldea Mani,
to give an idea immediately,
But he is no more!
How did he die?.
He died after drinking
illicit liquor.
Not only him, 18 people
died in our village.
What?.
Illicit liquor in our village.
All this happened
only in your absence.
Illicit liquor, prostitution...
... and gambling is
now very common here.
Who dares to do all these things?.
All in your family only.
Your uncle's sons are doing this.
Because they are your brothers...
... people are scared
to tell your father.
Do you know the rogues who
ran away fearing you,...
... have come back again
because of your brothers.
Padayappa please
listen to me, don't go.
Don't prevent me.
My path is different.
How dare you prepare illicit liquor?.
How dare you indulge
in prostitution?.
Just think of the
family you were born in.
If I see you like this again,
I'll thrash wherever I see you.
- What did I say?.
- You'll thrash wherever you see us.
- He is my friend, Alagapuram Alagesan.
- This face!?.
My friend will now
close his eyes,...
... when he opens you both
should not be seen here.
- One......
- They have vanished.
That's Padayappa.
Now people will have that fear in you.
- Sathvigam is coming.
Where?. Where?. - There.
Come on!
You won't get another
chance like this,...
... that girl is coming alone
so tell her about your love...
... ask her if she likes you too,...
... if she says yes
just hug and kiss her.
Will you do it correctly?.
Please don't make a mess of it.
Okay we'll go and hide.
Wait a minute, Padayappa wants
to talk to you so please wait.
- Oh no!
- Don't get scared, its a simple matter.
No, I'm very scared.
Then you seem to have
something in mind.
No, no nothing like that.
Then go and talk.
Go..... He's waiting......
Alright!
You wanted to talk
something with me....
Oh God!
He has messed it up!
Nothing.... Nothing is there?.
No nothing.
Then can I go?. You can go.
- Padayappa you spoilt the whole thing.
- What did I do?.
How much we told you.
What did you say?.
- Will you ask when we said?.
- When did you say it?.
Padayappa, we were
coming like this...
... and that girl
was walking towards
I can't explain everything again.
- Give that to him.
- What is this?.
- Love letter.
- Oh! That girl gave me?.
You only should write.
Me?. Here hold this,
let me tell you what to write.
Yes, tell me now, when you
meet her don't open your mouth.
Bend... now tell me.
Say it!
Yours lovingly, Padayappa.
Put your signature.
Take care else it may tear.
- Go give it and come.
- Me?. You go and give it yourself.
I can't go.
I'm not in love your the one.
- Aren't my friend?. Won't you
do this for me?. - Okay,come.
Wait. Tomorrow is an
auspicious day for Lord Muruga.
-... so lets give it tomorrow.
- This is the limit.
This is love, I'm going
to start a new life.
It's necessary to be sentimental
in these matters, isn't it?.
Now you'll talk well,
come there we'll see.
Give a lot of hay for the cow,
it'll give some extra milk.
Why are you whiling away your time?.
Are you here?.
I want to ask you something?.
If you put your hand into
the snake pit won't it bite?.
- What?.
- Didn't the snake bite Padayappa?.
- Go and ask him that question.
- Okay, I'll ask him.
Madam, please go inside, this
cow gets attracted to red color.
I can't were the
color the cow likes.
I'll do as I please, you
mind your own business.
Madam, please go inside.
Madam the cow......
Someone please help....
Bravo!
Did you give the letter?.
No.... Then give it now. Okay.
When your giving it mention
my name and give it.
- Okay...
- Think of God while giving.
Stupid not now, while giving.
Padayappa, come inside.
Yes, coming.
Padayappa asked me to
give you something.
- What?.
- This letter.
- Get a cup of coffee.
- Please help him God!
- Thanks for saving her life.
- Uncle, don't get emotional.
If something happens to
her, I can't bear it.
She is very dear to me!
- Ask him to sit.
- I forgot!
- Welcome sir.
- Didn't the snake bite you that day.
You don't bite him now.
You sit. He's my son's Secretary.
Welcome Padayappa, how are you?.
Fine. Your going to
be my brother-in-law.
- Is everyone fine at home?.
- Yes.
Mother asked if we have
to do anything special...
... for the engagement.
The girl itself is special
to us. So no formalities.
Am I right, Prakash?.
He's going to be a
groom so he's shy.
So how is your politics?.
This time they have
agreed to give me a seat.
You go inside and do your work.
She's very absentminded.
Have you seen your engagement dress?.
Yesterday I saw it.
It looks fine.
- Thats not yours, thats mine.
- No I saw it yesterday.
Try to understand what I'm saying.
Okay, okay.
I have some work so I'll take leave.
Even I have some work...sit down.
You carry on.
- Don't stand for everything.
- You didn't answer me.
Why do you respect
these servants?. Sit.
What are you waiting for?.
Keep it and go!
The fault is with me.
Don't get angry with her.
Girls should have
patience not anger....
...obedience not arrogance,
calm and not hasty.
A woman should be humble
and not audacious.
Altogether a girl should
behave like a girl.
It's believed that arrogant
women can't lead a happy life.
Since you want us
to walk like you,...
... do we have to walk behind you.
Today is his day so let him enjoy.
We feel very bad about it.
Why?. If Padayappa is
the man of power,...
... I am man of beauty.
The girl has escaped.....
Why do you say that?.
That girl will commit
suicide if she marries you.
Now if she see's you like this
she will refuse to marry you.
Padayappa, you give me your dress.
Ask someone else.
Only this dress looks good.
Then what will I wear.
You wear mine.
I can't. Padayappa my
marriage is important...
...or your dress is important.
How will that girl marry me.
Thats right.
Why don't you wash it and wear?.
If I have the time
why should I ask you.
Remove the dress.
We have to walk all the way...
... atleast we could
have taken a jeep.
Who will give us bride
if we go by jeep.
We should go by Benz
or Plymouth or else go walking.
- Are you going to see the bride.
- Why?. Have they gone away.
That's a good joke!
Is he the bridegroom?.
He's the bridegroom but the
dress he's wearing is mine.
- Thats why he looks good.
- Okay. Come, come.
Are you going to see the bride,
who's the bridegroom?.
He's the bridegroom but the
dress he's wearing is mine.
Thats why he looks tip top.
Padayappa I am only
the bridegroom...
... but this dress is mine.
Okay.
Who is the bridegroom in this crowd?.
He's the bridegroom but the
dress he's wearing is not mine.
Did he ask you about this dress?.
Don't talk about this
dress anymore. Okay.
The brides house is on this side.
There's some problem
with this glasses.
The bride is waiting
for you for a long time.
He's the bridegroom but l
won't talk about this dress.
Come here, come closer!
Padayappa, this dress is yours...
... but please forget about this dress.
Come lets go.
Who is the bridegroom in this crowd?.
You ask them yourself?.
Tell them...
He's the bridegroom but I forgot
about the dress he's wearing.
I think the bridegroom is mad.
Come lets go.
I don't want this dress
neither the marriage,...
... I'll remain a
bachelor all my life.
Don't worry Alagesa, the bride
will definitely like you.
If the bride agrees,
we'll fix the marriage immediately.
Padayappa, what you've
arranged to see so many girls.
You're very lucky select
any one from this.
I want to talk with you personally.
As soon as that girl signaled
all those girls vanished.
Don't disgust me before her.
Go from here.
This girl is dangerous
thats why we didn't go.
Don't get angry, we'll go.
Beware!
- You're very lucky.
- Why?. - Because I like you.
Seeing my beauty,
status and talent,...
... many guys more educated
than you liked me,...
... not only here but also abroad.
I was not interested
in them but I like you.
Aren't you lucky?.
In my childhood days I believe
I've played with you,...
... but I don't remember.
The world is changing
at a fast pace,...
... only fools remember old things.
I don't know why, when you saved
the snake I liked your bravery.
When you fought to
ban illicit liquor...
... I liked your anger,
And I admired your valour!
When you adviced me in my house
I admired the way you talk.
Most of all I like your style.
I admire your five
different faces,...
... your very lucky because
your the one I like.
I want every thing to be the
best in my life, my car,...
... dress, bungalow
and even my dog...
... and the man going to marry,
I want the best....
... I want to marry
someone like you...
... and stand before
my friends and society.
In your sisters engagement,
you express our wish.
You'll feel shy so I'll say it myself.
Bye.
You expressed your wish,
let me tell mine.
I'm not interested in marrying you.
You want to marry a man,
I want to marry a woman.
And that woman is not you.
Are you in love with someone?.
I usually don't desire for
anything but if I do,...
... I don't rest without getting it.
I'll definitely get you.
Baby, you said you've
seen my five faces....
I have another face,
don't see it, you'll regret it.
You'll never succeed!
You don't know about me.
My path is unique,
don't disturb that.
May I know the girl you love?.
Why do I have to wear a garland?.
Then only you'll look
like a bridegroom.
Everything is fine but we could
have had a small vocal concert.
- So what, I'll sing.
- What, you want to sing?.
- You thought my style is old?.
- You sing brother, old is gold.
- No, no, see he's sulking.
- Lets ask Padayappa to sing.
- Atleast today give that letter.
- Definitely I'll give it today.
Padayappa, your father's calling.
- What sort of a dress is this?.
- That's my style!
- Sing a song! - Me!?.
- They asked you to sing.
You have learnt music
formally, haven't you?.
Even your daughter
knows to dance,...
... Iet her dance
then my son will sing.
Are we going to have a competition?.
What rubbish?.
My sister refuses to dance.
Perhaps she has forgotten.
Son-in-law!
I mean, brother...
She's very moody so........
What a surprise!
How are you going to
manage such a huge crowd?.
After all we too have learnt music.
- What's this?.
- What's the matter?.
My son can manage
bigger crowd than this.
Make way!
- lsn't it Padayappa?.
- Thats right mother.
I'm ready to dance.
Even my son is ready to sing.
Isn't it son?.
- Yes father.
- Ask him to begin then.
She has studied in America
so she's very broadminded,...
... why are you
scolding him for that?.
He's not a baby, if that
girl has behaved like that...
... in front of thousand people,
there must be a reason.
- He hasn't done anything.
- Then, who did?.
- I need not say that.
- I'll slap you!
Why are you waiting, he'll keep
scolding you if your here.
Take care of yourself,
go care fully, eat properly...
...sleep at the right time.
Don't pamper him, did you give
those sweets you made for him.
- I forgot. - Go and get it.
- I'll bring it and come.
Did you pack his sweaters,
it'll be cold there.
I forgot.
Go bring it and come.
Go to bed early, don't
roam about in the nights.
Father, the village
elders have to see you.
Allow me to talk to him, will you?.
Okay, I'll come.
Son, come a week earlier
for your sister's marriage.
Don't worry about
anything I'll take care.
Its getting late you leave.
Good day, sir.
Welcome, welcome.
Whats the occasion?.
Why have you'll gathered here?.
You could have called
for me instead.
We've come to talk about
your family matter,...
... you are V. I. P.in this village.
What son, have you
done anything wrong?.
- No Father.
- lts not about him but about you.
There is a complaint on you.
Complaint on me?.
Who has given?.
Your brother only has given.
Father, father....
What has he accused me of?.
The property which
belongs to both...
... is being enjoyed only by you...
... and that you are lavish
in village activities.
Why are you keeping quiet?.
Nothing brother....
After giving the complaint,
why do you call him brother.
Ages ago two people
committed suicide...
... so my grandfather gave half
the property to the temple....
...and the rest is being used
for the welfare of the village.
I have three children,
don't I have to get them...
... married in a rich family?.
I don't get the same respect
as he gets in this village.
- They treat us a dump.
- It depends on each one's behaviour.
Why?.
- Proceed!
- What nonsense are you talking?.
I wanted to get my daughter
married to that rich man's son.
But before that he fixed
it for his daughter.
Atleast I thought I'll fix
my son for his daughter,...
... the way that girl
behaved yesterday,...
... I know even not going to happen.
Don't talk about all that,
tell your decision.
I want my share of
the property divided.
Brother, what do you mean?.
Only if I have money
people will respect me...
... and can get my children
married in a rich family.
You divide the property.
Are you sure you want
the property divided?.
Won't your brother
give you, if you ask?.
I'm not a beggar to go and ask him.
I was also born of my
mother not for someone else.
Yes, you were not
born for my mother.
You've provoked me to talk!
Your mother gave
birth to you and died.
I brought you to my house and
asked my mother to look after...
...you as she did to me.
She promised me that she would
never reveal this to anyone.
Till now no one knows about this,
I have not even told my wife.
Even you know it only now.
Only this man knows about this.
He was there when our father died.
Tell me brother, have l
ever called you by name,...
I pampered you so much!
... I love you so much...
... but you love only this property.
Everyone listen to me,...
... till I'm alive no on has the
right to divide this property.
Why should I divide it?.
Let my brother take everything.
I don't want a penny
from this property.
You take everything.
I will sign all the papers and give you.
If you don't have
anything what will you do?.
My only treasure is my son.
When he's there why
should I be bothered.
I've bought a piece of land in
the money he sent every month.
We will manage with that.
I don't mind living in a hut.
I'll prove my worth!
How am I going to
conduct this marriage?.
Go my son, from now on we are
all are at the back of you.
No father, you are
always our leader.
Wait, put the witness
signature and then go.
Padayappa, I know you'll
take care of your sister.
Make sure you take the
responsibilities which our...
... family has
undertaken from the past.
That's very important.
Wait a minute, let me sit
here for one last time.
What are you doing like a small child.
Come lets go.
- Father!
- Let's go!
Go and console your mother.
Are you still thinking of father.
I know your worried
about sister's marriage.
Don't worry I'll take care of that.
Padayappa, without
anyone's knowledge...
... your uncle's son
is getting married.
Who let all them inside?.
Ask everyone to get out.
Move everybody.
Its only a week since
your brother's death,...
... how can you do such
a thing in his house.
Stupid man, this is my house.
Why should I perform his last rites?.
Mind your own business.
How can you get you son
married to his daughter,...
... when he is engaged to this girl.
Yes, we engaged that girl to my
son when their family was rich.
How can I get my son married
to a family which is poor.
What will happen to
my family status.
I'm not a fool to get my
son married in this family.
Money will go and come anytime
but only relatives stay the last.
When your sister is like this,
how can you do such a thing.
Is wealth more important to you.
That's my wish, because l
wanted a break in politics...
... and since her father
had political influence...
... I agreed to marry her.
Now he's no more so
I changed my place.
I agreed not because I liked her.
Whatever the case may be,
according to our village rule...
... the marriage is
supposed to take place in...
...the temple with the bride...
... and the groom expressing
their wish to marry.
... and only then is the
marriage to be conducted.
- For how long?.
- Why waste time in arguments?.
Look, don't try to dominate us.
I spare you because of my sister.
God bless you!
She herself has
blessed the couple,...
... you people can go
and have your food now.
We are not so shameless
as to eat your food.
We're not beggars.
Come lets go, Padayappa.
If you don't eat, the food
is not going to get wasted.
Come, why are you so late?.
We were running out of time
since it was an urgent marriage.
I know you married only because
your parents forced you to.
Aren't you ashamed to
marry you don't like.
People like you encourage
such kind of male chauvinists.
Are you a man?.
Shame on you.
How selfish of you to
think only about yourself.
Oh! Are you still
thinking of Padayappa?.
I'll get you married to a
better person than Padayappa.
Why see other guys, see my sons.
You don't worry, I'll bring
thousand men for you to select.
You can bring thousand men but can
you find one man like Padayappa.
I'll marry only Padayappa.
No one can change this.
Why are you weeping like a child?.
But you're a child, aren't you?.
Eat this!
Mother is old so she weeps,
but why should you...
He should only cry,...
... for not being fortunate
enough to have you as his wife.
You don't cry, sister.
What big money, have we not
enjoyed all the luxuries in life.
See how grandly I'll
conduct your marriage.
I'll do more than what
father desired to do.
You eat.
I'll select a better man than him,
more educated, smart,...
... intelligent, good looking
and a man of your choice...
... but I can't get
the man you desired.
Alas! I can't get you
the man of your dreams!
I'm helpless dear!
Don't cry.....don't cry.
What will be our plight
if you lose heart?.
God is there to help
us so don't cry.
Please don't cry, my dears!
- Feed her.
- Eat my dear. - Eat my dear!
Why are you talking in English?.
Talk in tamil?.
This is granite stone.
I suspected it when
I saw it glitter.
Have you started your
family tradition?.
If you keep doing this,...
... you'll have to handover
the property to us.
Fools! do you know what
stone is that?. Granite.
So what?.
Idiots, you don't know
the value of this.
Drunkards, Padayappa has
a mountain of granites.
If he comes to know of this,
he can even buy the...
... villages surrounding us.
Now do you realise why l
gave that money to him.
Stupid fellows.
I shut his mouth for the time-being.
Okay, now what are you
going to do about it?.
Where is my brother's photo
which was hanging there?.
- You asked me to put it away.
- Hang it back there.
- Why?. - When we want their
favour, we need to do all this.
Brother, how can I forget you?.
Why are you crying father?.
I've just started acting,
stupid fellow, come.
Everyday brother
comes in my dream...
... and slaps me
exactly at 1 1 O'clock.
He treated me like his own...
... and gave me all the property...
... but his children
are struggling here.
- It's just a night mare.
- No it is not!
No, please come back to our house
otherwise you can't see me alive.
I will write all the property
back in your name.
It's your property any way.
You needn't come today, tomorrow
you can come after I handover...
... everything to you
in the register office.
Believe me, Padayappa!
See, I told you that your father
will never see us struggle.
See how he has changed him.
No mother.
Why should we struggle
here like this my son,...
... we'll go back to our house.
Let your father come
and tell this in your dream.
- Shut up. - Padayappa I'm like
your father, listen to me.
Believe me, son!
You may beat me for
the blunder I've made.
Fine, I'll beat myself!
- Stop it!
- I won't stop till he forgives me.
Is the slipper a new one?.
Is that very important now?.
Please believe me.
If mother agree's l
have nothing to say.
Thanks a lot. I'll transfer
all the property to your name.
Then I'll take leave.
Why don't you write this
piece of land in my name?.
I'll build a tomb in memory
of my dear brother...
... and worship him all my life.
Shall we fix the
registration tomorrow?.
Stop this nonsense!
Where is the party?.
My brother's tractor is an old one.
They are not coming in
Benz car like us,...
... the tractor is bad,
the road is bad.
More than that those
two guys are bad.
We can't go by the main road,
go through the village.
The registrar will be there
only for half an hour.
Come late in the Morning
and go early in the evening.
What happened?.
The bearing is cut.
It'll take atleast an
hour to set it right.
Don't go sir. Wait.....
Why are you so late?.
We came through a lot of hurdles.
Don't answer like school children.
We're only saying the truth!
Since its late the registrar
has gone home, so we'll have...
... the registration
tomorrow at our house.
Fine!
Everyone has signed in their
family, Mr.Aarupadayappan.
Go, son!
Catch it.
Collect all the important documents.
Close all the windows.
Stop my son.
Don't sign.
This is the third time
we are facing a hurdle.
I don't think it's a good omen!
Let them keep the property.
- Come lets go.
- Alright! - Please wait.
I want to fulfil my brother's dream.
We have all signed,
what do I do with the papers now.
- Tear it off?.
- Explain to them!.
You please tear it!
Padayappa from the time you
beat them they are like this.
If there's a wind it'll blow.
The tractor was old so it broke
down don't take this as a reason.
Whatever you say,
please let us go.
My mother has decided,
so please let us go.
Let's go!
I think you desire something else?.
I need that piece of land
you now or not even that...
... I just need that small hill
in the middle of the land.
Why do you need that alone?.
With that alone, I can
buy the whole village.
Why did someone tell you,
there is a treasure?.
That's not an ordinary hill,
that hill is made of granite.
- Only that god has helped us.
- Better bestow that hill to me.
- Otherwise?. - My sons are
not worthy to beat you...
... so I've set up
people from outside.
Padayappa, don't make it
too long, finish them...
... and come home quickly.
Okay mother.
Alright, mother!
Where are you going?.
Please complete the formalities.
Let me go!
Gone are the days when people
were treated as slaves!
Slaves are non-existent these days.
You'll suffer for the
sins you've committed.
I don't interfere with
anyone but if they do.
I think you understand.
My path is unique, don't forget.
Go and ask forgiveness.
Padayappa, please forgive me.
Forgiveness is only to those
who sin unintentionally.
I'll even forgive my
deadly enemy but not you.
Don't ever face me again
for the rest of your life.
If you do, you won't be alive.
Please wait, I want to talk to you.
I don't know how to tell you
the first time I saw you,...
... I fell in love with you.
I get nervous whenever I see you!
I decided that I'll marry only you.
Even now I'm telling you,
I won't leave you.
If you ask her directly,
how will she tell you.
Write a letter, she'll reply back.
For the past two years,
he's been giving that letter.
What to do, I don't
get the opportunity.
- Shut up, you'll never give.
- I'll definitely give it today.
Let's see.
- Why have you come?.
- Is your mother there?.
- Yes. Why?. - I want to meet her.
- You can't.
Brother, why are you
standing outside, come in.
Now can I go inside?.
- How are you?.
- Fine brother. - Go inside.
There's no point in
wearing a shawl,...
... if you don't
know how to wear it.
Always put it the right way.
How did you hold the snake?.
- Let's go inside.
- Why?.
- We'll see what they've come for.
- Your right sometimes.
What brother, everyone's
seeing the house...
... and your looking at the floor?.
Brother, why are you crying?.
What happened?.
My daughter's life is in your hands.
Why?.
Tell me what happened?.
- You know how much I love
my daughter. - Yes, I do!
Her life is in your hands now.
Is my face worse than a servant.
She's very adamant about
marrying only Padayappa.
I couldn't convince
her regarding this.
If we leave her like this,
she'll die of depression.
Please accept her as
your daughter-in-law.
Please don't let my sister
suffer for what I did.
Please don't spoil her life.
I'll fall on your feet.
Don't worry brother,...
... tomorrow I'll come to your
house to fix the marriage.
Padayappa, do you agree?.
If you agree,...
... I have no objection!
I'm very happy.
Are you crying?.
What's your status
and what's my status.
You can only build
castles in the air.
Your wishes can never be fulfilled.
But if I desire something,
I will definitely get it.
Don't let your tears dirty
my nail, keep it clean.
Welcome, welcome.
- Shut up! You please come!
- Welcome!
Why are you standing there?.
Come in.
There isn't enough space
to accommodate all of us.
I think sister has still
not forgotten the past.
No, no, let's exchange the
plates in front of everyone.
Definitely.
Go bring the plate and come.
Come sister,
lets exchange the plates.
I'm a widow, so I can't.
Whatever it is you're
my sister, come.
Give the plate.
I'm willing to get
my son Padayappa...
... married to your
daughter Vasundara.
If you're willing,
please accept this.
Why are you scared?.
No one can do anything to us.
God and my son are
always by our side...
... so, if you're
willing, accept this.
That's a good shot!
You said that it doesn't matter
even if I'm a widow, right?.
I was a widow the other day when
you severed relations with me.
You showed your true
colour that day.
That day I was poor
so you neglected me.
That's why you fell on my leg
yesterday so shamelessly.
Okay, you didn't respect me...
... but do you remember the
promise you gave my husband...
... before this village do you
remember to keep up the promise.
Only if your a human being,
you'll remember all that.
You can ask me, what happened
to the promise that I gave you.
I'm not like you, my family
always keeps up its promises.
My family is a respectable family.
Yesterday I promised to
come to your house...
... but not to fix
up your daughter.
You might have changed our
village's tradition...
... during your son's
marriage but I can't do that.
My husband's words
still echo in my ears.
... that only if the
bride and groom agree,...
... the marriage will take place.
Even though your son
liked my daughter...
... he married another girl
for the sake of money...
... but my son agreed to
marry your daughter,...
... only because I told him.
I can't be a mother if
I can't understand him.
I know who he's in love with.
My son is like a camphor
whether your rich or poor,...
... if you light him,
he'll give you only one light.
How could I afford to hurt
my son's feelings then?.
Padayappa, go bring
my daughter-in-law.
Being a woman,
she boldly spoke to him.
He couldn't reply her
for even one question.
I'd have died of shame!
That day he spoke so much,
now who will marry his daughter.
He gave more importance
to money, didn't he?.
What can money do now,
his respect is gone.
If you can't keep up a
word it's better to die.
Character is very important!
If character is lost
everything is lost.
Oh God!
Father.
Neelambari, what's this?.
Come in.
Are you mad?.
Why are you dancing like this?.
Yes, I'm mad, I'm angry.
I'm angry with that servant.
- I want to own Padayappa.
- What can your anger do now?.
That servant dog even though
she knew that I liked him...
... and still went behind him.
I won't leave her, not only
her but also Padayappa...
... and his mother who were the
cause for our father's death.
I'll avenge this insult!
He's walked away with that girl,
what can you do now?.
This Neelambari can do anything.
All because of me,
I refused to marry his sister,...
... now he has done the same thing.
No, Padayappa loved Vasundara
even before your marriage.
Okay, so what can we do?.
Tell me, shall l
bring him here now?.
Padayappa is a mountain
you can't bring him here.
You can't even touch him!
You don't know when,
where and what to do.
I know how to deal with this matter.
I won't let this
marriage take place.
That day in my desire to own him,
I tied this anklets on my legs.
Today, I tied it
because of my hatred.
Just the way this anklet
deserves to be tied on my feet.
Similarly, Padayappa too
deserves to live on my mercy.
Till I own him, I will not
remove this anklet from my leg.
This is a promise.
Don't want, why should
you touch my leg.
Vasundara, hereafter your
the master of this house,...
... so we should only
be scared of you.
Brother, wait a minute,
see how your wife is feeling shy.
Before the marriage itself
if she's like this,...
... you'll be able to see
her face only after 3 months.
She'll show her face
but he's only very shy.
Bridegroom, look at her.
Are you feeling shy?.
Look at her!
- Are you fine?.
- I'm fine aunty.
- I came to see Vasundra.
- Go and see.
- Welcome.
- How many months?.
Wait, I'll bring coffee for you.
- Go carefully.
- Sit down.
Please be seated!
Now you're not my servant,
your servant to him alone.
But you're very clever!
Very smartly you hid your feelings.
Please forgive me.
I too loved Padayappa,
but it didn't happen.
Things happen according
to God's will.
Vasundra, now your our girl so
the dowry'll come from our house.
But father has just expired
so I can't do all that.
As a sister I've brought
this saree for you,...
... I've also arranged
for a pooja in your name.
Wear it and go to the temple.
Get up, don't make me feel big.
I'm also a small girl, take this.
Cow! Please help!
Someone please come and help.
Hurry, sister-in-law!
Help!
Is it enough?. It's getting
late quickly tie your saree.
I'll tie it myself,
you people wait outside.
- Why shouldn't we be here?.
- No, no, you wait outside.
Why are standing here?.
Go outside.
I'm sorry for giving
that red saree,...
... I would have spoilt your life.
It's alright!
This is the offering l
made to God on your behalf!
Please have it.
I'll keep it in front of
God and then drink it.
- This is special milk, so make
sure you drink it. - Okay.
Don't forget to come for our marriage,
I need your blessings.
The marriage thats going
to take place is mine,...
... my family's marriage so
without me it can't take place.
I'll definitely be there!
- You look very good. - Me?.
- Not you, sir you turn around.
How did you put your
hand into the snake pit.
Shut up and go that side.
What snake?.
When did you catch?.
Okay, okay, don't get tensed,
the bride will come now.
- Didn't you drink that milk?.
- No!
I kept the milk in front
of God and was praying,...
... the snake came
and spilt the milk.
Only then I remembered
that I've prayed to God...
... that I would pour milk on God.
That's why I went to...
- Hurry, it's getting late.
- Coming, wait a minute.
In the name of Lord Muruga l
ask you, according tell me...
... would you like to marry
this boy wholeheartedly.
Do you also agree wholeheartedly?.
What is this?.
Forget the past!
We brought you to Madras to
forget whatever happened.
Why you are seeing the
same thing again and again?.
Your health will get affected if
you starve, so have some food!
- No.
- Are you Mad?.
Yes! I am Mad, I will not
look at any one of your faces!
I've not only been humiliated
but I've been defeated too.
I've lost to a servant!
I don't know that you
love him this much!
Anyhow, I will bring Him to You!
You want me to be in
the place of a Servant?.
Is it possible for
You to imagine This?.
Are you My Brother?.
- How can you think like this?.
- Neelambari! - Tell Me!
Everything happened
are because of you,...
Because of your money
making intention!
Go!.. Go all of you!
Don't look at my face.
If anyone of you look at my face,
I will burn my face.
Get out! Get out!
Get out all of you!
Long live, Suryaprakash!
Long live our leader, Suryaprakash!
Long live our honourable
minister, Suryaprakash!
Not for One year, or Two years!
She kept herself in that
room for eighteen years!
She has confined
herself to that room.
She doesn't permit anyone
into the room except me.
With my growing wealth I have
made many changes to house.
But I can not change her room alone!
I can't change her.
All these are also okay.
But she didn't come out
for Mother's death too!
I used to take meals to her room,
that too if she asks!
If his daughter or any other
person takes meal for her...
... she will throw the plate away.
We are not aware of
any of her activities.
But we can able to here playing
sound of that Marriage cassette.
- lnspector's here.
- CM is in the Meeting. Can we go?. - Yes!
Don't forget things
that I told you,...
You can do any pooja'
at whatever be the cost.
She should change,
that is important.
This should not be known to others.
Uncle CM has begun the
meeting, I'll make a move.
- The matter that I told you...
- Are you playing?.
If your sons were held up because
of doing unnecessary Business.
What can I do?. That too they've
borrowed from Krishnaswamy!
Son-in-law, everything has gone.
Only thing left is that house alone.
If that house is also gone,
then I'll have to stand in the road.
Please try to get back
atleast the house, son-in-law.
Think of what all I've done
for you and my daughter.
What to think of!
He has influence till Delhi.
If I talk about him to CM,
my post will be in danger.
- Bye!
- Coffee...
Give it to Daddy, dear.
Shall I leave.
- Greetings!
- Make way!
It's time to go for meeting.
Get in, we'll start.
Sir, I'll fall on your leg.
Please ask them to stop!
Daddy, my doll.
I want my doll.
Some how I'll try to return
your loans sir, please.
You're keep on telling
that you'll return,...
... but you are not giving and
I'm not getting, what to do...
We've been living in this
house for a long time.
If people come to know of this,
it'll be a big shame for us, sir.
I know, since it's a old
traditional house,...
... that's why I gave you money.
My brother lived with great
dignity in this house.
Give me some time.
Somehow I'll fill all my loan.
How! Will you steal!
You might do that also...
What to do!
The due date is over.
Now you have no other go.
Not even God can protect you.
Who gave it?.
Hey, stop it.
Take everything inside.
Madam, please go in.
Couldn't you tell me this before.
If I have influence all
over the country,...
... he has it all over the world.
I have national business,
he has international business.
He is a mighty influential person!
You were about to put me in trouble.
Please go in sir.
Hey, keep everything
in it's place and come.
Where are you producing trouble?.
Do you know whose house is this?.
I know, I heard that you
had problem with them...
... and so you will not interfere.
Whatever has to come to
you is here with interest.
Count and see if it is correct
and bring the documents.
You give everything
countless we follow you...
... how can I count your money.
Hey, bring the documents.
Oh, I shouted out of habit sorry.
You go sir, I myself
will arrange everything.
Hey take everything.
Keep them in their own places.
There is no history
that a greedy man...
... and a loud woman
have ever lived happily.
This is the place where my
father had lived and died.
For me this is his memorial.
Atleast from now,
take care of it carefully.
You have given it already.
That is to save the house,
this is to save you.
- Padayappa...
- You are an elder man.
We're elder only in age.
But are elder in heart,
so you are a great.
- Forgive me.
- Forgive us also brother.
Uncle, remember one thing in life.
You'll get nothing without hardwork.
Anything you get without
hardwork will never last.
Listen.
Please see this.
Hey, why are you showing hand?..
If you show hand,
we'll be terrified?.
Give it, we'll accept it!
Hey, our children.
It was you.
Enough...enough...enough.
Enough of studying in Madras.
Hereafter learn to do
the household chores.
Daddy, see daddy.
Only 2 years course. Tell her.
What?.
You have influence only outside.
House is under mother's control?.
Mummy, sister likes to learn.
If you had a boy you would
let him to learn isn't it!
All you need is an assistant, isn't it?.
I'll stop studying.
You can act well though
you can't study.
Correct, like your mother.
What yes..yes...yes... Tell there.
It's a matter of 2 years, after all.
Daddy... Please.
Vasu...Vasu... Let her study further.
Ok, let her study.
They are my friends.
They've come for my birthday.
- Greetings!
- He's my Dad.
What do they say?.
I'm a worldwide fraud.
You show me your fraud.
You mixed brandy, isn't?.
You and your sons drink illicit liquor.
Do I drink it.
We drank once upon a time.
Now we've changed know!
What change... See
here... brandy bottle.
If Padayappa comes to know of this,..
- He will kill you.
How will he know when I've
mixed it with cool drinks?.
- lt'll smell. - I'll put betelnuts.
- I'll tell him.
I'll tell him that you
bought me betelnuts.
Who am l?.
Alagapuri Alagesan.
Then mixed it with colour,
you'll never know it.
You'll never know it.
Like monkey spoiling
itself and others,...
... you are spoiling others also.
- What I'm spoiling others?.
- Yes. - See there!
- Welcome, Welcome.
Hello. Anitha - Daddy...
- Mr. Ravi Chellaiya.
- Greetings! - My Daughter.
Many happy returns of the day.
Small gift for you.
Move... move...
Longlive leader...
Longlive minister...
move... move...
Greetings Padayappa.
Where is it.?.
Where is it... Garland.
Take it.
take it...
Take this Madam.
Cover...cover...
Hey take it. Hello, when did you come.
I didn't notice you.
Give it!
He's Mr. Ravi Chellaiya.
Longlive... Ionglive...
Garland...Emperor of industries.
Longlive...Ionglive...
You sit sir.
Hey...go apart.
Always shouting.
Hey tell him about me.
My early days friend.
Name Rajbagadur.
You can call him anyway.
I told him not to join politics.
He didn't listen.
Did you listen to me?.
He refuses to join politics.
Why, you don't want me to be fine?.
Why you alone should be fine?.
People also should be fine no.
Yes. You are correct.
But one thing.
If he comes with you,
you might change him.
Is he going to change?.
He'll change all of us.
That is also correct.
You win in everything.
Why don't you try this also.
What is there in our hands,
Mr. Ravi. Everything.
- Always lift your hand up.
- Shall we start the party?.
- I should get the seat first.
- Calm down!
Be seated.
I told to start the birthday party.
Anyway, you have to start a party.
Are you going to Himalayas?.
Will we leave you?.
Hey, what are you doing here?.
- We were drinking cool drinks.
- What cool drinks?.
Nobody is there to welcome
guests, you're busy drinking?.
Give it and go.
What noise?.
Nothing.
Padayappa drank the cool drinks.
What...what... Haven't l
drunk cool drinks before.
Give it.
- It's two now.
- What two.
I'll drink four, forty.
What bothers you?. Give it.
What happened?.
It's nice.
Brother, come here.
It's getting late to cut the cake.
- I'm coming. Go. It's nice,
keep it for me. - I will!
No, mother first,
all next including God.
Yes.
It's eighteen years.
Still you think of him and make
your life miserable like a mad.
But he.
He is happy, very very happy.
See this, see this well.
He, his wife, his two
daughters are enjoying life.
But you! Day and night you sit
in the same room like a devil...
... sleeplessly thinking
of him get destroyed.
I've never seen, heard or learned
in history about a girl like you.
Enough. enough.
Atleast hereafter try to be happy.
Even I tried to ruin
him in many ways.
Using my political influence
I tried to make the...
...government take over
his granite factory.
I couldn't. He is brilliant.
Nothing is there in his name.
He has everything in the
name of his village people.
If police enters, the
whole village is opposing.
Government is nothing in
front of people's power.
We can never ruin him.
Forget everything.
Opposing him is useless.
We can't take revenge on him.
For how many days will you
keep on seeing his marriage.
He himself has daughters
ready for marriage.
His daughter is studying with
my son in the same college.
What are you looking at?.
After eighteen years I've
got another chance...
... to take revenge on Padayappa.
- Where is the dressing room?.
- There.
Call your son.
Hey, Chandru.
What Daddy?.
Wow aunty, you are super.
When I was small I used to peep
through the door with fear.
- But now... - Do you know to drive?.
- He is an expert.
- But we have many drivers.
- Let him drive.
You too come with us.
That girl in violet is Anitha.
Padayappa uncle's daughter.
Hereafter she shouldn't smile.
That servant's daughter
should not be happy.
Padayappa's loving
daughter should cry.
Your son should love that girl.
She should also love your son.
Should act as if he is in love.
Understood?.
Don't worry. My son will
act according to your wish.
He knows that you are
very dear to me.
If he doesn't do it, I will
strangle his neck and kill him.
Why are staring?.
Do what I say. Start!
- How, how... how?.
- Hey, No Chandru don't.
Why do you cry now?.
Have I come to seperate
you and Chandru?.
I've come to unite you two.
Don't worry.
You and my brother's son
will definitely marry.
Even your father can't stop it.
No aunty.
You don't know about my dad.
I don't know?.
What do you know?.
I heard that you were not
in town for eighteen years.
If you were here, we would've
been like family friends.
his marriage would have been easier.
What happened now?.
Everything will be easy.
This time, what I think
should definitely happen.
- Madam, you've got a phone call.
- I'll talk and come.
- Still daughter is not on line?.
- They've gone to call her.
Brother, will Anitha accept?.
Why do you worry?.
She's my daughter.
I am your dad speaking.
Hello dad.
Daddy. How are you...
I'm fine dear, how are you?.
It's too many days since I saw you.
I want to see you immediately.
I wish to see you married soon!
No no, your mother wishes.
- Lie...
- No...your father is willing.
Murugesa... beat him you
know who is the groom...
... none other then
my sister's son.
We all wish that you
two should get married.
But according to
our village customs,...
... the bride and the groom
should like each other.
That's why I asked your wish.
What do you say?.
What are you thinking of?.
Because the boy is not educated?.
You have studied no...
Both should not be educated.
If so, there will be confusion.
Now see I and your
mother are so happy.
Why, I'm educated.
But she is not. That's why.
Shall we have the
marriage after your exams?.
- Now say yes to your dad.
- Why?.
Has the line been cut?.
- No. The lights are on.
- It is a phone, not current.
I'll explain everything later.
First say yes.
- Yes dad.
- Give your hand.
So shall I start the
arrangements for the marriage.
- Marriage. - Tell him that
everything is as per his wish.
- How... Tell what I say...
- Okay dad, as you wish.
Wow... my darling...
She's my daughter after all!
What son-in-law, are you happy?.
See how I'm going to
make the wedding grand.
Hey Alagesa, Murugesa,
Hang garlands on every street,...
... house and doors.
None of our ancestors should have
ever conducted such a marriage.
I will conduct such
a grand marriage.
Do you want to possess
Chandru whom you love most...
... and wish to get
married grandly...
...in the presence of your
parents in your village?.
Then listen to me.
In the name of Lord
Muruga I ask you,...
... according your
self-conscious,...
... and on the promise
of Aarupadayyapan's...
...tell me would you like to
marry this girl wholeheartedly.
Yes Uncle.
Yes Sir.
In the name of the Lord,...
... do you also agree to
marry this boy wholeheartedly?.
- Tell me.
- I don't agree, sir.
Why no?.
Didn't they seek your consent.
That day's situation made me accept.
Why you didn't like this groom?.
I'm in love with another boy.
I like to marry him.
Okay, is that boy present
in this crowd?. Tell.
Madam! Tell me if you
want only this girl...
... to be your daughter-in-law?.
Nothing like that, brother.
I want my son to
become your son-in-law.
Take the garland from
your shoulders...
... and put it on your
sister's shoulders.
Do as I say!
- Do you consent to marry this girl?.
- Yes sir.
You... Don't be afraid of anybody.
Tell me what you feel.
I like the groom.
But I don't like to marry now.
What do you say?.
I don't want to get married
before my sister's marriage.
If we marry on the same
day also no problem.
But if it happens before her,
it might affect her marriage.
Please tell your decision.
I can't change the
traditional rituals.
Every marriage that takes place
in this village should be...
...according to the
wish of the bride...
... and the groom
than their parents.
No unwilling should take
place in this village.
Such a marriage will not
be conducted by my family.
Open that well!
From the time he
started conducting...
... the village's marriage the
well was not at all opened.
Today because of his daughters,
the well has to be opened.
You know the rules of this village.
Marry your girl to whom she loves.
If you get her married
to somebody else,...
... your family cannot
live in this village.
I won't take it as a shame
for whatever happened here.
I take it as a chance to
know my two daughter's mind.
Now I tell in front
of all of you,...
I'll conduct the marriage of my
elder daughter with the boy...
...she likes, here, in
the next auspicious day.
On the same day my
second daughter...
... will get married
to my sister's son.
If it does not happen,...
... it means that Padayappa's
breath has stopped.
I swear on Lord Muruga!
Tell me. Open your mouth and answer.
Why did you do this?.
I don't oppose your affair.
But why didn't you
tell when we asked?.
Do you know how much
shame you brought to him.
I'm asking you,
why don't you answer?.
No mummy. They told me not to
tell the truth till the end.
Who said so?.
What Neelambari has to
do with your marriage?.
I love her brother's son.
Why didn't you tell this before?.
If I tell this, daddy will
not accept for the marriage.
If I tell my wish infront
of the villagers,...
... in the temple of
Aarupadayappa,...
... nobody can stop but.get me
married to the person you love.
Neelambari aunty said this.
She told me she'll come with her
brother's son for marriage,...
... but never turned up.
- Come here!
- Go, he is calling you.
- What is his name?.
- Chandru.
- How did you get introduced?.
- We study in the same college.
- Does he love you?.
- Yes dad.
- How do you know?.
- I'm your daughter.
I'll never get fooled.
Forgive me dad.
When you start to love,
you forget your parents.
When you love,
you forget yourself.
Don't forget love after marriage.
Children might forget
their parents...
... but parents will never
forget their children.
Take the car.
You don't go there.
Please listen to me..
No, listen please...
- Madam, Padayappa has come.
- Who?.
That is our great Padayappa.
You know how he looks at this
age also like Margandeyan.
Ok mam.
Yes mam.
- Ask him to come inside.
- Alright.
Please come in!
One minute please.
Didn't the snake bite when you
put your hand into the pit.
- Yes, it bit. - It bit?.
Then poison would got in.
No snake poison would
get into this body.
Big snake is going to come.
Be careful.
Electrifying man, you know
why everybody likes you...
... though aged, your style
and beauty has not gone.
Thank you thank you... It's
born with me, never goes out.
How is she, the servant of my house?.
Sorry, the madam of my house.
Very very fine.
- Why did you come to see me?.
- I didn't come to see you.
I came to see my
would-be son-in-law.
- Your son-in-law?.
- Yes.
My daughter loved him.
He also loved her.
Chandru loves your daughter?.
Who asked you to come in?.
Security, what are you doing?.
Why did you make him to sit?.
Why are you shouting?.
Call your son.
He wants to talk to him.
Why, what does he want
to talk to my son?.
- Call him. - How are you?.
- I'm fine brother.
Dad, did you call me?.
Your uncle has come to talk to you.
Uncle?. Suppose he'd married
you I can call him uncle...
... because he's my aunt's husband.
- Now why... uncle.
- You didn't understand.
He wants to get you
married to his daughter...
... and become your father-in-law.
His daughter is not
lucky enough for that.
He only told that you and his
daughter love each other.
Many girls love me in college.
But I should love them, isn't it?.
If his daughter loves me,
ask her to come. I'll keep her.
As a servant.
Marriage invitation.
It's for you. Take it.
You know who's getting married?.
It's between my do
you know Umanath,...
... a hundred times richer
than you, his daughter.
Don't definitely come for marriage.
It's a minister's home wedding.
They won't let you in.
You know the date of marriage?.
Remember your promise in
front of all the villagers,'
' In the next auspicious date...
... I'll conduct the
marriage of my two daughters.
If it does not happen,
it means that Padayappa's...
... breath has stopped'.
That same day,
Remember, when you
stopped my marriage.
My dad also bowed his head like
this, thinking of his daughter.
As my father hanged himself...
... when he could not
keep up his promise,...
... you should also hang
yourself in shame...
... in front of the villagers.
Seeing that, I should feel happy.
Only then, my father's
soul will rest in peace.
As I suffered for not
getting the one I loved,...
Similarly, your daughter too
should suffer all her life.
My servant who is your
wife now, should cry...
... over her daughter's
plight, all her life.
That's the pleasure
Neelambari will derive...
... after 1 8 years of
self-imposed exile.
You boast that your path
is unique, don't you?.
My path too is unique!
You can't outsmart me, anymore!
Bravo! That was a
master plan indeed.
You'll be a very
successful politician.
This is the first time
it has slipped, isn't it?.
I change towels often
but I don't lose them.
You keep it safely too!
Do you think I've
forgotten the past?.
A politician may fail
to keep promises...
... but he will never
fail to avenge his insult.
Open the door,
Padayappa is leaving.
I'm your daughter,
I surely won't get cheated.
Why haven't you returned yet?.
What took you so long?.
Did you call for us urgently?.
What's the matter?.
Ask Vasundara to make
arrangements for the marriage.
Are you sure?.
- Don't you know my nature?.
- But everything is in their favour.
But God is in our favour!
Padayappa and his men may
come in disguise, be careful.
Don't worry, I'll take care!
Did you check the kitchen?.
Are they keeping a watching?.
Are the Mufty cops indoors?.
Padayappa has arrived!
You aren't permitted to go inside.
- Why?.
- Do you have an invitation?.
That's irrelevant!
Drive him away!
- He's uninvited!
- That's right!
In fact I've come to invite!
- Whom?.
- Son-in-law!
My son-in-law!
But why do you want to take him?.
Because this marriage
is against his wishes.
- Who said so?.
- The groom himself said so.
- My son!?. - Yes, Honourable
Minister's only son.
Why are you silent?.
Speak up!
- I'll tell you.
- Hey! Who are you?.
Why have you abducted me?.
Don't you know who I am?.
We know you, but you should know
of one man who's very popular.
Look there!
Are you trying to threaten me?.
- My father has many henchmen.
- They aren't henchmen.
They are my friends!
I too have a gang of
men who obey my orders.
Your father's henchmen are cowards.
But my men are brave.
But I've never misused their
services for my selfish motive.
I'm good to those who are good to me.
And you too are good.
I know that.
Tell me the truth.
- Weren't you involved with my daughter?.
- No!
- Didn't you love her?.
- Didn't you promise to marry her?.
- No!
- Didn't you love her?.
- No! Not at all!
Your daughter isn't worthy of me.
Why have you stopped?.
Face her boldly...
... and repeat what
you just told me.
Pardon me, uncle!
They asked me to pretend to love
Anitha, but I loved her truly.
If my father and Neelambari
know of this, they'll kill me.
You should help us unite!
It slips only once!
Father!
Finally you joined
him to stage a drama.
No. One hit, not even one hit
should fall on my son-in-law.
Mr.Suryaprakash,
care for your son's life.
Don't listen to others to
make his life miserable.
You are in a responsible post.
Don't misuse it.
Don't spoil the name of your party.
Enough of your advice.
He is my son. I'll compel him to marry.
If something happens
to my son-in-law,...
... then anything might happen here.
What will you do?.
Ever tell what I'll
do and how I'll do,...
... you'll know when it happen.
If a single man comes and do
riots in the minister's house,...
... you'll keep quiet?.
Beat and chase him out.
Yes, I'm a single man.
But to give their life to...
this single man,...... just peep
and see how many are there.
Hey, how so much of crowd
come into the city?.
They forcibly entered as farmers.
See the Padayappa's army.
This is only a trailer.
You've not seen the main picture.
If you see it, you'll be shaken.
You have political influence.
I have people's influence.
You live on police's power.
I live on people's power.
Infront of this power,
your power is nothing.
Let us see if your power is
strong or mine is strong.
What are you looking,
shoot everybody.
How many will you shoot
how many will you shoot.
See how many police do
you have, how many guns...
...and how many bullets in it.
How many people can you shoot?.
Do a small calculation and see.
If you shoot some also,
the others will smash you.
Come to our side,
or else you'll also die.
I won't mind that you
are my father-in-law.
I'll die peacefully by being
a slipper to this man...
... rather than being a
father-in-law to a man like you.
Life will go at anytime.
Let it go after uniting
such a good pair.
Shoot me!
Come on lG sir,
give the shooting order.
If you shoot four people,
others will run.
Hey, those who run and jump
are on your side, politics.
Those on this side
are faithful ones.
If Padayappa says a word,
we won't shout,...
... but tear you into piece.
Don't try to test our man.
If you try it, we will do anything.
What do you say?.
What are you waiting for?.
It's an order!
Sir, why do you think
it is so simple.
See there.
Already the press people are writing...
... about what's happening here.
Onething if you wish, I can only
stop them from getting inside...
... and secure you, that's all.
If something happens tomorrow,
I can't answer CM, sir.
Try to convince your son
and get him married.
What trying to convince him?.
If the groom is not interested
how will you get him married.
Have we come to watch it
and give Rs.5 and Rs. 10 as gift.
We are silent because
you are a police...
...otherwise we would
have torn you into pieces.
Tell them brother.
My brother's smile is more than enough.
Silently send the groom.
The groom, brother-in-law,
father-in-law are against you.
This is your family problem, sir.
Don't make it a
politics sir, please.
Mr. Padayappa, there
should be no problem here.
If the groom agrees,
you can take him with you.
- Do you wish to go with him?.
- Yes.
This is POLlCE.
You would now remember the
drama you staged by fooling...
... and stopping my
daughter's wedding.
Once you won.
Good. I woke up.
Now you would have understood
my way is a unique way.
Tell all our partymen
and blackcats...
... that my son's funeral might
take place but not this wedding.
I'm also coming.
Take the car.
Hey, cut to the left.
Put the brake and lift to the left.
Then, what hobbies.
Sports uncle.
What game do you like?.
Cricket...then... hockey,
then... batmintion, tennis uncle...
I like football See
how it is flying.
We can't sir.
Come back!
You lived in city.
Will you like villages.
Wherever Anitha is,
I like it uncle.
Hey, there is a pit.
Put the brake and lift.
He escaped!
- He escaped from us also, over.
- Go fast!
See he is coming, hit his car.
No you are the groom.
Why you go to this rowdies.
You sit.
I'll tackle them.
- I've mastered this art.
- No, uncle you are aged.
Am I you sit inside
and watch my age.
Sit son-in-law!
You are not aged.
A lady is coming with a gun.
What are you looking at?.
Come all of you.
Whatever happens here, nobody
should move from their place.
Forgive me Padayappa.
No I'm worthless even
to say your name.
Since I couldn't possess you...
... I tried to ruin
you and your family.
But I failed.
Even now, I tried to kill
you infront of your eyes.
Still you tried to save me.
So you are not a human,
you are a God.
You thought I would say that.
Never.
I'm not an ordinary woman.
This anger will not
end in eighteen,...
... twenty years not
till the end of life...
... not even if my life ends.
I'm not servant Vasundra to
live with a life you gave me.
Hey, you won in this birth.
If there is a rebirth,...
... this Neelambari will
definitely take revenge on you.
Though how many times
you take rebirth,...
... a greedy man and a loud
woman have never been happy...
...there is no such history.
You didn't live happily
when you were alive.
Atleast let your soul rest in peace.
God.
There are thousands
of obstacles in life.
Obstacles are your stepping stone.
There are thousands
of obstacles in life.
Obstacles are your stepping stone.